David Luong

Location: New York, NY | Mobile: 917-818-9212 | Email: davez2015@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/davidluong1

Professional Summary

Creative IT student with a passion for Front End Web development, Web architecture, Mobile apps, and User Experience (UX). Fascinated by the impact developers and UX designers have on everyday lives through websites and mobile apps via the internet. Interested in honing professional communication in order to better understand different types of clients, and satisfy their needs to the best of my ability.

Education

Rochester Institute of Technology

Rochester, NY

B.S. in Web and Mobile Computing (formerly Information Technology), GPA: 3.08 (2015 - 2020)

Skills

Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS3, SQL, Unobtrusive JavaScript, Java, PHP, C#

Libraries/Frameworks: Bootstrap, jQuery, Foundation

Tools/Software: Sublime Text, MySQL, Microsoft Visual Studio, jGRASP, NinjaMock, Photoshop, Illustrator, GitHub

Other: Mathematics, Microsoft Office, Google Drive, Windows 7, Windows 8, Research

Work Experience

CareerVillage.org

Product Tester (3x/week, 2hr/day)

Jan 2017 - Present

- Testing prototypes (mobile apps) designed by the organization's UX team, and offering feedback based on my experience with the team's design.
- Completing online surveys on the prototypes to enhance UX design.
- Examining and proofreading PDF documents for grammatical errors.

Community Volunteer (5x/week, at least 1hr/day)

May 2016 - Present

- Creating, and posting career-based questions for students on the organization's forum page.
- Answering mostly general, college-based questions that students, educators, and professionals, are posting to the site.

RIT Office of Career Services and Co-Op

Career Fair Volunteer (once per month, 3hrs/fair)

Mar. 2016 - May. 2016

- Leading prospective employers of various companies to their correct booth.
- Unloading prospective employers' supplies, and answering their questions.
- Providing prospective employers additional supplies: business cards, brochures, flyers; and chairs.

The New York Public Library

Volunteer (at least 30 hrs/week)

June 2014 - Aug. 2014

- Shelved books, CD's, and DVD's based on Dewey Decimal Classification.
- Placed items on hold for patrons.
- Checking items in and out of the library.
- Guided children, and their guardians around the library.